You know our school is an  international school -  it's a Canadian school
你知道我们的学校是一所国际学校 - 这 是一所加拿大学校，
but full of students from different countries, which is
但学生来自不同国家，这是
very unique
非常独特。
Finishing, high school at Bodwell is a very significant milestone
从博域中学毕业是一个非常重要的里程碑，
For our graduates it's much more than finishing their study,
对于我们的毕业生来说，这不仅仅是完成了他们的学习，
it is finishing an important stage of life.
而是完成人生的一个重要阶段。
Students, who board at the school gain a lot of life experience
在学校寄宿的学生获得很多生活经验，
that we need to stretch our imaginations to understand
我们需要用一些想像力来理解。
Of course they experience a lot of laughter, fun and excitement
当然，在学校和宿舍的每一天，
in school and in the residence every day.
他们经历了很多欢笑、喜乐和兴奋。
However there are moments of sadness and loneliness
然而，当他们中的一些人想家时，
when some of them miss home,
有一些悲伤和孤独的时刻；
others not used to the new food, the new situations, and the new people.
其他人也许不习惯学校提供的膳食、新的环境、和陌生人。
Overall, our graduates achieve a much higher level
但总的来说，与其他同龄人相比，
of self-management, confidence, and maturity
我们的毕业生在自我管理、自信和成熟方面，
compared to other students of similar age. I admire them.
达到了一个更高的水平。我很佩服他们，
I truly do.
真的。
They learn to solve problems and they learn to be independent
他们学会解决问题，并学会独立，
It is much more than academic achievement that our graduates should be proud of.
毕业生应该为此感到骄傲，这远远超过学术成就。
These students, who come, from home they share this diverse and rich
这些来自不同家乡的学生，
socio- cultural environment at Bodwell.
在博域分享这个多元化和丰富的社会文化环境。
I urge you to pay attention to what our graduates say today.
我敦促你们关注我们的毕业生今天所说的话。
What they say about their life  and about their aspirations.
他们对他们的生活和他们的愿望所说的话。
Learning to respect people's
学会尊重其他人，
people's cultural beliefs and
的文化信仰
The way they see the world in from their eyes and their perspective
和他们从自己的眼睛,和角度看世界
Perspective
视角
People and students from all other
这些来不同
backgrounds, cultures,  and ethnicities
背景,文化和种族的学生，
that come together and make a community
他们聚集在一起并建立了一个社群。
Community
社群
The greatest lesson i've learned, while I've been here is to be your open-minded and respectful
我在这里学到的，是你们的开放和尊重、
Patience, tolerance, and just how to be myself around other people
耐心、宽容、以及如何在其他人中间建立自己
Cooperation,
合作、
Identity
认同、
Knowing that everyone is equal
知道每个人都是平等的、
Perseverance
毅力、
Tolerance
宽容、
My leadership skills
领导能力
Courage
勇气、
Harmony
和谐、
To respect other's cultures
尊重他人的文化、
I learned how to respect their beliefs
学会如何尊重他人的信仰。
Respect respect respect
尊重, 尊重, 尊重
Another lesson i've learned is maturity
我学到逐渐 成熟，
Independence is very important for a boarding high school student
学会独立对寄宿生来说非常重要。
I came to Bodwell and I became an independent person
来到博域，我成了一个独立的人。
I see myself impacting, greatly, the lives of young people.
我看到自己很大程度上振奋了别人的生命。
I see myself running for president in Mexico
我看到自己在墨西哥竞选总统。
I want to be someone who helps other people
我想成为一个能够帮助别人的人。
..as a cardiac surgeon saving lives every single day
…作为一名心脏外科医生，每一天都可以拯救生命。
...always wanted to become a pilot
…一直想成为一名飞行员
Film Editor
或者一名电影编导
I will become a lawyer
我将成为一名律师。
I want to be an architect when I grow up
长大后我想成为一名建筑师。
A journalist
…一名记者。
Surrounded by people I love
…被我爱的人包围。
I think the greatest lesson I've learned from my time here
我认为我在这里学到的最重要的一课，
No matter where you're from or what language you speak,
无论你来自哪里，或者说什么语言，
we can still all work together to make a better world tomorrow.
我们仍然可以共同努力，在为明天创造一个更美好的世界。
This environment inspired me a lot.
这个环境很大地激励了我。
I'm proud of myself.
我为自己感到骄傲。